"lang"
{
"Language" "English"
"Tokens"
{

// mr_tf_english 3
"Pony_Desc_14"                           "Press Primary Attack to ready your pony, then press Secondary Attack to charge!"
"Pony_Desc_15"                           "Press and hold Primary Attack to ready your pony, then press Secondary Attack to charge!"
"Pony_Desc_16"                           "Press and hold Primary Attack to charge!"

}
}
